{
    "subject": "resource/Cercospora_apii",
    "predicate": "property/classis",
    "object": "resource/Dothideomycetes",
    "human_readable": "Cercospora api is classified as Dothideomycetes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6872584819793701,
            "question": "To which taxonomic group are Dothideomycetes classified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.650969386100769,
            "question": "What fungal class does Cercospora api belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5504836440086365,
            "question": "How is the classification of fungi like Cercospora api determined?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44830337166786194,
            "question": "What is the significance of classifying organisms into taxonomic groups like Dothideomycetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4437091052532196,
            "question": "Can you name a characteristic feature of fungi in the Dothideomycetes class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43594372272491455,
            "question": "How are fungi in the Dothideomycetes class typically found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43557390570640564,
            "question": "Are there any other examples of fungi within the Dothideomycetes class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37792643904685974,
            "question": "Are there any known diseases caused by Cercospora api?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3321172297000885,
            "question": "What methods are used to study and understand fungi in the Dothideomycetes class?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3036436438560486,
            "question": "What are the ecological roles of fungi like Cercospora api?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cercospora api is classified as Dothideomycetes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_191_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What methods are used to study and understand fungi in the Dothideomycetes class?",
            "html": "dbpedia_191_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any known diseases caused by Cercospora api?",
            "html": "dbpedia_191_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other examples of fungi within the Dothideomycetes class?",
            "html": "dbpedia_191_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_191_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to try another query!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the response to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of \"Cercospora api\" in the documents. However, it is mentioned that Cercospora is a genus within Dothideomycetes (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_191/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided includes discussions on various genera within the class Dothideomycetes, including examples of species such as Ascochyta and Cercospora. The mention of Cercospora in this context supports the statement that it is classified under the Dothideomycetes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about Cercospora api being classified as Dothideomycetes, whereas the context clearly mentions that Ascochyta, not Cercospora, has an unstable taxonomy history.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}